<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[@palebluedev's blog]]></title><description><![CDATA[A technical blog about technical computer things]]></description><link>https://palebluedev.github.io/blog</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2019 00:23:23 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title><![CDATA[Lessons learned whilst creating this blog.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Test in another browser (a bug it seems is causing brave to endlessly refresh in develop) When setting up a project always declare somewhere…]]></description><link>https://palebluedev.github.io/blog/lessons-learned-whilst-creating-this-blog/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://palebluedev.github.io/blog/lessons-learned-whilst-creating-this-blog/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2019 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Test in another browser (a bug it seems is causing brave to endlessly refresh in develop)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;When setting up a project always declare somewhere the node version that is going to be used&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Github pages will only deploy your pages when a new push has been made to github pages, so if you were pointing at master /docs and changed it in settings to gh-pages, you’ll need to do another push for the changes to be visible. Otherwise you’ll just get a 404.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Please allow me to introduce myself.]]></title><description><![CDATA[I’ve been a software engineer for over 5 years now, it started out as a hobby and grew into something more
than I could have ever dreamed…]]></description><link>https://palebluedev.github.io/blog/introducing-my-self/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://palebluedev.github.io/blog/introducing-my-self/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2019 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;I’ve been a software engineer for over 5 years now, it started out as a hobby and grew into something more
than I could have ever dreamed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;So with that said what do I want to do with this blog?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Theres nothing revolutionary I’m trying to do here, I want to help other people who might be looking for answers and myself with something to look
back at.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Why not use my real name?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The’re two main reasons for this, one I don’t care to build a personal brand, two I understand the dangers of the internet I will accept criticism for sure but I’m not going to open myself up to personal attacks. This obviously has its downsides in the sense that my credibility is an unknown quantity but I’m fine with that.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>